pcaobus.org 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy

This website, www.pcaobus.org, is the site of the Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (the “PCAOB”). This policy applies to the privacy practices used on our site.

In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or providing personal information about yourself. At various places on our site, however, we tell you how to contact us and we encourage you to provide us with some details about yourself, such as your name, address, or phone number. We may gather and retain such personal information that you have voluntarily submitted. In addition, registration applicants provide us with requested information as part of our online registration process.

Principal reasons for our request for information are to enable us to respond to comments, questions, and complaints, to obtain the perspectives of people interested in the PCAOB’s rulemaking and other activities, to effectuate the registration process, and otherwise to carry out our statutory duties. Also, we may use information that has been provided in order to contact you or to provide you with information that we believe may be relevant to you.

### Disclosure of Information

The Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002 governs the circumstances under which the PCAOB may disclose certain information. Except as provided in this federal statute or otherwise required by law, the PCAOB does not agree to limit its use of the information you provide unless we explicitly agree in writing to do so.

### Security Measures

The PCAOB takes reasonable steps to protect the information you give us from unauthorized access during transmission. We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you submit to us when you submit registration materials using our secure registration system.  The PCAOB also tracks site-access statistical information to maintain site security, to enhance features we provide to our site visitors, and for information regarding the nature and extent of our site's usage. We currently do not use “cookies” on our site.

### E-Mail Communications

The PCAOB does not automatically track the e-mail addresses of its website visitors. We may, however, collect the e-mail addresses included in e-mail communications that are forwarded to us. As with all Internet e-mail, e-mail you send us may not be secure from interception prior to receipt. If you wish to communicate with us in an alternative manner, please contact us via mail or telephone.

### Links

Our site may contain links to other websites. When you go to other sites through these links, you are no longer on our site and are therefore no longer covered by the PCAOB’s privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites and we do not control the information submitted to, or collected on, these sites or the use or disclosure of such information. We therefore encourage you to read the privacy policy of the sites to which you are linked before supplying information.

### Contact Information

If you feel that there has been a breach of security on this site, please contact the PCAOB Security Management Office at the e-mail address or phone number below. Please report any technical difficulties you may have with the operation of our site to our Webmaster.

#### PCAOB Security Management Office

  * Phone: (202) 207-9100

### Children's Privacy

We do not collect information through our site from those actually known to be under the age of 13 and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

### Modifications to this Policy

The PCAOB may modify or rescind this policy at any time without prior notice. Any such modification or rescission will apply only to information that is provided or confirmed to us after the effective date of the modification or rescission. We advise you to review this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended, prior to providing or confirming any personal or sensitive information.
